<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Okal Otieno</title>
    <link>https://okal.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Okal Otieno</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 14:07:05 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://okal.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://okal.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 03:54:38 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://okal.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there. My name is Okal Otieno. I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer with product experience spanning financial services, data collection and visualisation, messaging, and EdTech. I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in roles ranging from hands-on development, and architecture, to engineering management. Even the odd bit of UI/UX design in a past life. I currently work as a Tech Lead at JUMO, a financial services technology company.
This blog is a catalogue of the joys, frustrations, and - hopefully - brief moments of insight that come with my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Python Static Analysis</title>
      <link>https://okal.me/posts/adventures-in-python-static-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 14:07:05 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://okal.me/posts/adventures-in-python-static-analysis/</guid>
      <description>I had an opportunity, in mid-2017, to work on tooling to weed out dead code from one of the codebases I work on at Jumo¹. We use an in-house framework for building USSD² applications, the main mode of interaction users have with our lending platform.
There isn’t much of a FOSS USSD ecosystem, so the framework had to solve a lot of basic problems in novel ways. Some of the most interesting aspects of it have to do with session management - USSD being a stateless protocol without any widely adopted session management standards, and a metaclass³ based routing model.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>